<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aayush</title>
    <link>http://localhost:51330/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aayush</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:00:03 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:51330/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Problems with Reels and Instagram Propaganda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/posts/reels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:00:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/posts/reels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let me share something deeply troubling I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on Instagram recently. This app is very popular among the Indian youth, and many people use it religiously, like every day from dusk till dawn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s most concerning is the content being churned out by creators, especially in the &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;reels&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; or short video format. So there are various types of creators on this platform, but we&amp;rsquo;re seeing a disturbing trend where people are going to shocking extremes for views—from dangerous stunts to outright self-harm; &lt;em&gt;some are eating literal shit, bathing with gutter water, having abusive fights, and doing things for content that can cause harm to their child only&lt;/em&gt;. Even more alarming are parents who put their &lt;strong&gt;children&lt;/strong&gt; at risk for content, filming while their toddlers teeter on the edge of beds or wander dangerously close to traffic. The pursuit of viral fame has completely overwhelmed basic parental instincts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverted Quarantine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/posts/inverted-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/posts/inverted-quarantine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently heard this term when I was reading about how people managing their health in polluted environment like Delhi where AQI crossed 1000. This term immediately caught my attention, as this is very relevant in current scenario. Basically in short, it describes how affluent classes are separating themself from pollution impact and creating safe space at home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, quarantine involves isolating a source of harm to protect the public. In contrast, inverted quarantine involves creating personal safe spaces within polluted environments. With air purifiers, bottled water and organic food, affluent individuals build a ‘commodity bubble’ to shield themselves from environmental hazards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitalism VS Communism: Who killed more ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/posts/capitalism-vs-communism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:11:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/posts/capitalism-vs-communism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;has-capitalism-killed-more-people-than-communism-throughout-history&#34;&gt;Has capitalism killed more people than communism throughout history?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TLDR;  without a doubt… there’s never been a world war because of communism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now lets dive into details. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen many arguments agains communism that says -  Mao &amp;ldquo;killed 40 million&amp;rdquo; and is thus eviler than Hitler who &amp;ldquo;killed 12 million&amp;rdquo;. The modern day &amp;ldquo;death toll contests&amp;rdquo; spawned from boomer-tier memes comparing &amp;ldquo;evil dictators death counts&amp;rdquo; are pointless and devoid of context. Yet ignoring that these roundups tend to undercount victims of Nazism, the deaths in China were due to mismanagement and incompetence. The deaths from Nazi Germany were a deliberate policy of starvation and mass slaughter meant to enslave and exterminate inferior races. Nazism also only operated its genocide for 6 years before it was stopped, Hitler himself in power for only 12 years, compared to Mao ruling for several decades. Nazism likely would have killed tens of millions more, again, deliberately, if it had lasted longer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Argument</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/posts/privacy-argument/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:17:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/posts/privacy-argument/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-your-argument-to-i-have-nothing-to-hide&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s your argument to &amp;ldquo;I have nothing to hide&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am by far the most privacy oriented of my friends, and whenever they see me use Firefox or do something other than the norm for privacy They just say, &amp;ldquo;I have nothing to hide&amp;rdquo;. What do you say when someone does this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;focusing-on-hiding-is-the-wrong-attitude&#34;&gt;Focusing on &amp;ldquo;hiding&amp;rdquo; is the wrong attitude&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, &amp;ldquo;Privacy&amp;rdquo; is just the right to control your own data and your public image.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitalism is a Driving Force of Climate Change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/posts/capitalism-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 12:33:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/posts/capitalism-climate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Unseen Consequences of Capitalism on the Environment and Society&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the world grapples with the challenges of climate change, economic growth, and social inequality, it is essential to examine the underlying drivers of these issues. The pursuit of economic growth and profit has led to a paradoxical situation where the very systems designed to benefit humanity are instead contributing to its demise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cost of Progress&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The relentless drive for economic growth and consumption has resulted in the depletion of natural resources, pollution, and the loss of biodiversity. The production of goods and services has become a never-ending cycle of exploitation, where the costs are borne by the planet and its inhabitants, rather than the corporations and individuals reaping the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:51330/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51330/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, and my name is on top of the site. I am a 24 old guy from India, who loves computers and softwares. I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer and graphic designer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But most importantly &lt;code&gt;I am a man of culture.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a generalist, focusing on a great user experience. People like to complicate things, I don&amp;rsquo;t.
I deeply believe that simplicity is the key to making great products. I love Minimalism.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
